My book came in today. I was going to do a post about it. And then I saw this and it really just took the joy and the steam out of it. But I'm putting together my book tour.
We want to do a stop in the Bay. A prominent black bookstore said that even though I would be providing my own books, that if they could not take a cut of my books, then they weren't interested in hosting me to do a book signing because they said if it don't make dollars, it don't make sense.
So my socialist mind doesn't think that way. The way I think is where's the symbiosis? To me, the symbiosis is I will be bringing people who like books to a place that sells books and the place that sells books would be allowing me to sell my book in their space.
And to me, that feels like symbiosis to many, to others, it may not. That being said, if you are in the Bay and you would like to host me to do a book signing of my book, What Would the Ancestors Say that I have self-published?
After I bought my memoir back from Simon & Schuster, I decided to actually write, lay out, and self-publish a book that I felt was more appropriate for these times.
These are dark times. These are frightening times. And these are times where I feel like we need to actually realign with ancestral teachings, with our empathy, with our community, etc.
And What Would the Ancestors Say is a text that is all about that.
If you are in the Bay and you would like to host me and the people who want to buy my book and you would allow me to take 100% of my sales because I have put 100% of my soul into this,
I promise you the people who come to buy my book will also absolutely patronize your store because that's the kind of people that buy my book.
So drop a comment and I will DM you. Thanks.
If you do want to see me in my full excitement, you can go to my Patreon where I went live when it arrived.